[{"answer": "Two people aren't breathing.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "911 OPERATOR: What's the problem?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "It was James Ray's version of a Native American sweat lodge ceremony where temperature's reportedly reached 120 degrees killing three of his followers and sending 19 to the hospital.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "911OPERATOR: A sweat lodge?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, I'm doing pretty well, Piers.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "How are you in yourself and what do you feel about it all now that you served your punishment?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, if I can back up a little bit.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What was going through your head when you heard guilty negligent homicide?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "You know, it's interesting, Piers, that the first month that I was in and that was the better part of the first month.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "And what was the reality, how was she when you were in prison?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "You know, hindsight is 20/20 and there's a lot of things that I wish were different.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "When you look back on it, what is the single biggest regret about any aspect of the preparation, the planning, any of the things that led to these people dying?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "How does that happen in such an environment?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "They sweat, right?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, obviously not good enough, you know.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "So what kind of barriers or controls that you have in practice given that it was clearly, potentially dangerous?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, you really don't know how hot.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Was there a heat limit that you used to have for the sweat lodge?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "There's no regulation for a lodge.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Why was there no regulation?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't know nor did anyone know that anyone was in a death -- in a life or death situation.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Again, why didn't you do that?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Well I was in the lodge running the lodge which the prayers and the affirmations and all those types of things.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "You?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "I don't recall that at all, Piers.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "And if is so why?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I do and I recall people leaving.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Did you recall anybody saying to you, \"I've got to be out of here\"?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "AMES RAY: Some people wanted to quickly exit and one of the things I told them in the set up was to go our clockwise carefully because obviously there's a pit of hot rocks in the center.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Were they panicky?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "There were people positioned within the lodged that were supposed to take care of the participants.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What was the system in place for that kind of eventuality?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Two people aren't breathing.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "911 OPERATOR: What's the problem?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "He made one comment and they did say, \"She's passed out, she's passed out, I don't know if she's breathing\", and he said \"The door has now closed and this round has begun, we'll deal with that at the end of this round.\"", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "911 OPERATOR: A sweat lodge?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I understand.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What do say to that?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "I don't know, Piers.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Did you make yourself subliminally cut corners?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Shocked, denial, disbelief I couldn't comprehend it, anguish.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "When you were told that people have died, three people have died, what was your immediate reaction?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "It was my event.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Do you fell guilty for what happened?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "You know, Piers I wish I could say that I was enlightened enough to not have any impulse for self-preservation, I'm not.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "That there was an allegation that you left the scene pretty quickly, and just disappeared, is that true, and if so why did you leave so fast?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "There was definitely character traits in me that hadn't changed and there's still are.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Did you look back at yourself with a certain degree of disgust perhaps at your actions and recognize that there was a character trait in you that you had to change?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I had to play mental games with myself because I had to wear shackles to the shower.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "And when you find yourself on those first few weeks as you've said on with death row inmates is about as low as your life could possibly have gotten coming from down this huge high, what the hell were you thinking as you've said in yourself?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Well, humbling.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Humiliating?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "First of all again, I'd say I'm sorry.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "What would you say to them?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "... stuff, you thought about that?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Everything.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Did you lose everything financially?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Millions.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "ORGAN: How much did you have before all this?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "You know it's a lot of my money was tied up in my business and in hard assets.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "10, 20 million?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I have no complaints.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "But do you think looking back it was an appropriate punishment given that three people had paid money to be in your tutelage lost their lives?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "She's in that category, you know.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "And this lady that you came with tonight?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "AY: My mom is my greatest supporter.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "I mean, now to see you were talking very emotionally about her at the start of the interview, when you came out what did she say to you?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Yeah, of course Piers.", "docId": "131125pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Samantha, first thing's first, do you ever have doubts about dating the George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 461}]